<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wilderness Downtown</title><link>https://julianyap.com/</link><description>Recent content on Wilderness Downtown</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Julian Yap</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:08:45 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://julianyap.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arch Linux - Surface Book 3</title><link>https://julianyap.com/pages/2024-04-04-1712257725/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:08:45 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/pages/2024-04-04-1712257725/</guid><description>I have installed Arch Linux on a Microsoft Surface Book 3 to use as my &amp;ldquo;focus&amp;rdquo; machine. This page outlines some things I&amp;rsquo;ve had to install and tweak.
Most everything works out of the box except the cameras. Suspend (which works inconsistently) also eats up 20%+ of the battery life overnight.
This is not a recommended laptop for running Linux.
Visual Studio Code hangs on launch Had this issue.
Work around add to ~/.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin ETF flow bot - Methodology</title><link>https://julianyap.com/pages/2024-03-13-1710370430/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:53:50 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/pages/2024-03-13-1710370430/</guid><description>Introduction My Bitcoin ETF flow bot which posts updates at the X account @ubiqetfbot works by scraping the associated web sites of the ETFs to gather the updated reported Bitcoin holdings in the respective fund/trust.
Specific details for each ETF is outlined below (in alphabetical order by Ticker).
Details ARKB - ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF Data is from their fund web site.
Historically, the holdings are updated 10+ hours after the close of trading.</description></item><item><title>Tweeting images with Golang</title><link>https://julianyap.com/posts/2024-03-13-1710365831/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:37:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/posts/2024-03-13-1710365831/</guid><description>Introduction X (the website formerly known as Twitter) has gone through certain &amp;ldquo;changes&amp;rdquo; in recent years. At some point they introduced the v2 API but the functionality isn&amp;rsquo;t complete.
The v1 API needs to be used for uploading media and getting the resulting media ID. We then need to use the v2 API to reference the uploaded media ID to finalize the post.
Media upload For the v1 API media upload I utilize this library: github.</description></item><item><title>Litecoin (LTC) - MimbleWimble transactions using Regtest network</title><link>https://julianyap.com/posts/2022-07-24-1658648241/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:37:22 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/posts/2022-07-24-1658648241/</guid><description>Introduction Litecoin has implemented MimbleWimble using an Extension Blocks sidechain, commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;MWEB&amp;rdquo;. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any references to using MWEB other than articles which delve more into the technology but not the day to day wallet interaction. This post utilizes the standalone private Regtest network to demonstrate the usage. There are Additional links and references at the bottom of this post if you need an overview of the technology.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://julianyap.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 22:24:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/about/</guid><description>By design.
No analytics.
No promises.</description></item><item><title>First post</title><link>https://julianyap.com/posts/2022-05-15-1652658630/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:29:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://julianyap.com/posts/2022-05-15-1652658630/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve never liked the static site generator Jekyll (being Ruby) that comes with built-in support from GitHub. With the advent of GitHub Actions, this has allowed me to set this site up with Hugo and an auto-deployment.
Definitely not sure what content I want to put up on this site. I&amp;rsquo;ve built it and blown it up a few times.
The content creation process has been a long term concern of mine.</description></item></channel></rss>